("Man, I Feel like a Woman")
- Let's go, girls
(loud guitar music)
Come on
(upbeat country music)
♪ I'm going out tonight ♪
♪ I'm feelin' alright ♪
♪ Gonna let it all hang out ♪
♪ Wanna make some noise ♪
♪ Really raise my voice ♪
♪ Yeah, I wanna
scream and shout ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ No inhibitions ♪
♪ Make no conditions ♪
♪ Get a little outta line ♪
♪ I ain't gonna act
politically correct ♪
♪ I only wanna
have a good time ♪
♪ The best thing
about being a woman ♪
♪ Is the prerogative to
have a little fun and ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, go totally crazy ♪
♪ Forget I'm a lady ♪
♪ Men's shirts, short skirts ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, really go wild ♪
♪ Yeah, doin' it in style ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, get
in the action ♪
♪ Feel the attraction ♪
♪ Color my hair,
do what I dare ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, I wanna be free ♪
♪ Yeah, to feel the way I feel ♪
♪ Man, I feel like a woman ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ The girls need a break ♪
♪ Tonight we're gonna take ♪
♪ The chance to get
out on the town ♪
♪ We don't need romance ♪
♪ We only wanna dance ♪
♪ We're gonna let
our hair hang down ♪
♪ The best thing
about being a woman ♪
♪ Is the prerogative to
have a little fun and ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, go totally crazy ♪
♪ Forget I'm a lady ♪
♪ Men's shirts, short skirts ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, really go wild ♪
♪ Yeah, doin' it in style ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh,
get in the action ♪
♪ Feel the attraction ♪
♪ Color my hair,
do what I dare ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, I wanna be free ♪
♪ Yeah, to feel the way I feel ♪
♪ Man, I feel like a woman ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ The best thing
about being a woman ♪
♪ Is the prerogative to have
a little fun, fun, fun ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, go totally crazy ♪
♪ Forget I'm a lady ♪
♪ Men's shirts, short skirts ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, really go wild ♪
♪ Yeah, doin' it in style ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh,
get in the action ♪
♪ Feel the attraction ♪
♪ Color my hair,
do what I dare ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, I wanna be free ♪
♪ Yeah, to feel the way I
feel, to feel the way I feel ♪
♪ Man, I feel like a woman ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Oh, oh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I get totally crazy ♪
♪ Can you feel it ♪
♪ Come, come, come on, baby ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ I feel like a woman ♪